tropicalsmoothiecafe.com 2017-10-14

# Tropical Smoothie Cafe · Privacy Policy · Eat Better. Feel Better.

## Privacy Policy

Tropical Smoothie Cafe, LLC is committed to protecting the privacy of our customers and users of our websites. This page presents our internet privacy policy. 

####  1\. Types of Information We Collect and How It Is Used 

Tropical Smoothie Cafe only gathers personal information, such as first and last names, addresses, email addresses and mobile numbers when voluntarily submitted by you. For example, personal information may be collected from you in order to get your feedback on our website and our products or to enter you in one of our contests or sweepstakes. 

####  2\. Sharing of Personal Information 

Tropical Smoothie Cafe may share personal information within affiliated companies that we own or control, as well our franchisees. Any affiliated companies and franchisees must comply with our privacy policy. 

We may also share personal information with other companies engaged by us to perform a variety of functions, such as fulfilling orders, assisting with promotions, providing technical services for our websites, etc. These companies may have access to personal information if needed to perform such functions. However, these companies may only use such personal information for the purpose of performing that function and may not use it for any other purpose. 

Tropical Smoothie Cafe reserves the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request, to protect the integrity of the site, to fulfill your requests, or to cooperate in any law enforcement investigation or an investigation on a matter of public safety. 

We do not sell, transfer or disclose personal information to any other company without your permission, except as described above. 

####  3\. Children’s Privacy Notice 

This Children’s Privacy Notice is designed to answer your questions regarding our practices with respect to personal information we collect through our websites from children under the age of 13. 

What Personal Information Does Tropical Smoothie Cafe Collect? We may offer features on our websites, like games, which do not require a child to provide any personal information. On occasion, however, we may collect personal information, such as an email address, from children as part of an activity. 

For example: 

We may collect a child’s email address to notify the child if he or she has won or lost a contest or sweepstakes. In that event, we will notify the child using the email address the child supplies. We will not keep the address or use it for any other purpose. 

We may collect a child’s email address in order to respond to a request from the child on a one-time basis. In this case we promptly delete the email address from our system once we have responded, and we do not use the address for any other purpose. 

We will not collect other personal information from a child under the age of 13, such as a postal address or telephone number, without the consent of a parent or guardian. If parent or guardian consent is required we will collect the email address of the parent or guardian so we can provide notice of our information practices and/or seek the parent’s or guardian’s consent. Tropical Smoothie Cafe will not condition a child’s participation in any online activity on the child’s disclosure of more personal information than is reasonably necessary to participate in that activity. 

How Does Tropical Smoothie Cafe Use the Personal Information It Collects? We use email addresses submitted by a child in order to respond to the child’s request or to notify the child if he or she has won or lost a contest or sweepstakes they entered. We use the email address of a parent or guardian, in order to provide the parent notice of our information practices or to seek the parent’s or guardian’s consent. 

How Does Tropical Smoothie Cafe Share Personal Information? We may share a child’s personal information with third parties to the extent reasonably necessary to protect the security or integrity of our sites, take precautions against liability, or respond to judicial process or requests from other governmental authorities; or when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity. 

We also may share personal information collected from children with vendors that perform services for Tropical Smoothie Cafe. These services may include hosting our Website, providing technical services to Tropical Smoothie Cafe, fulfilling requests or administering sweepstakes. Such vendors are obligated to protect the confidentiality of the personal information we share with them. 

Requests from Parents Regarding Our Children’s Privacy Practices: Parents may review personal information we have collected from their child that has not been deleted, and can request that the personal information be deleted from our records if it has not been already. Parents also may refuse to permit further collection or use of their child’s personal information, when the parent has previously provided consent. To do so, please contact us at the address, telephone number or email address provided below with your request. 

Who Should I Contact with Questions? If you have any questions about our Children’s Privacy Notice, please contact us at: 

Tropical Smoothie Cafe  
1117 Perimeter Center West  
Suite W200  
Atlanta, GA 30338  
Telephone: (770) 821-1900  
Email: [info@tropicalsmoothie.com](mailto:info@tropicalsmoothie.com)

####  4\. Access 

If at any time you would like to correct the personal information we have about you or if you would like to change your preferences for contacts from us or on behalf of our business partners, you can let us know by contacting us at the email or postal address listed below. 

####  5\. Cookies 

“Cookies” are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies allow the website to remember information that will make the individual’s use of the site more convenient. Like many websites, Tropical Smoothie Cafe uses cookies for a variety of purposes in order to improve your on-line experience. For example, we track the total number of visitors to our site on an anonymous aggregate basis. We may also employ cookies so that we remember you when you return to the site, to keep track of the items in your shopping cart if you purchase merchandise online, to administer certain contests and sweepstakes and to help customize your Tropical Smoothie Cafe web experience. We may associate personal information with a cookie file in those instances. 

Use the options in your web browser if you do not wish to receive a cookie or if you wish to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie. Click on the “Help” section of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences. If you disable all cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of all the features of this website. 

#### 6\. Google

Our website utilizes google remarketing. As a visitor to our website you should be aware that your data may be used in the manner articulated below. 

Where users have chosen to enable Google to associate their web and app browsing history with their Google account, and to use information from their Google account to personalize ads they see across the web, Google will use data from its signed-in users together with our Google Analytics data to build and define audience lists for cross-device remarketing. In order to support this feature, Google Analytics will collect these users' Google-authenticated identifiers, which are Google's personal data, and temporarily join them to your Google Analytics data in order to populate your audiences.

####  7\. Links to Other Sites 

We may offer links to sites that are not operated by Tropical Smoothie Cafe. If you visit one of these linked sites, you should review their privacy and other policies. We are not responsible for the policies and practices of other companies, and any information you submit to those companies is subject to their privacy policies. 

####  8\. Changes to our Privacy Policy 

This privacy policy is effective as of April 28, 2017. If we change our policy, we will post the revised version here. 

####  9\. How to Contact Us 

Tropical Smoothie Cafe Corporate Support Center  
1117 Perimeter Center West  
Suite W200  
Atlanta, GA 30338  
Telephone: (770) 821-1900  
Email: [info@tropicalsmoothie.com](mailto:info@tropicalsmoothie.com)

#### More About Tropical Smoothie Cafe
